[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jackie Chan appears in all these movies but one. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Iron Monkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Enter the Phoenix", "The Myth", "Rush Hour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many students had to spend their Saturday in detention in the movie The Breakfast Club?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["7", "8", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is the Gonimbrasia belina, popular food among the native inhabitants of South Africa?", "correct_answer": "Moth", "incorrect_answers": ["Cricket", "Snake", "Frog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of the traps that must be overcome in the movie The Last Crusade before getting to the Holy Grail?", "correct_answer": "The Cup of God", "incorrect_answers": ["The Path of God", "The Name of God", "The Breath of God"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the characters in the film Snakes on a Plane was bitten by a snake on the chest but was not harmed because he was wearing a bulletproof vest?", "correct_answer": "Sean Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Troy", "Neville Flynn", "Eddie Kim"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A sea wasp is a jellyfish.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Emphysema is a chronic disease affecting the organs of which system of the body?", "correct_answer": "Respiratory system", "incorrect_answers": ["Skeletal system", "Urinary system", "Digestive system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which mammal has the most teeth?", "correct_answer": "The spinner dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["The tiger seal", "The dingo", "The giant armadillo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Friedkin moved to Hollywood in 1965. In 1967 he released his first feature, Good Times, starring this famous duo.", "correct_answer": "Sonny and Cher", "incorrect_answers": ["The Captain and Tennille", "Diana Ross and Marvin Gaye", "Elvis Presley and Nancy Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these rivers runs through the Czech Republic and Germany?", "correct_answer": "Elbe River", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhine River", "Danube River", "Rhone River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Batmans original name, when he first appeared in DC comics?", "correct_answer": "The Bat-man", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman", "Dark Avenger", "The Dark Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This ritual is part of the traditions and culture of the Minoan civilization, discovered by archaeologist Sir Arthur Evans.", "correct_answer": "Bull-leaping", "incorrect_answers": ["Fire-dancing", "Cockfighting", "None of these"]}]